{
    "id": "d75e73f53a854fc4a28917ce887ec0de",
    "title": "Has vs. Have vs. Had",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Rita …………………. a pet dog.",
            "description": "Use has with singular subjects.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "871aabe68b984aca9a473976c39d1976"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. a strange experience yesterday.",
            "description": "Yesterday shows past time hence, we use had here.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "18e5097028aa499591d10875a6aa4981"
        },
        {
            "question": "My neighbour …………………. a farmhouse.",
            "description": "Use has with singular subjects.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9a036db4a95647b2a806beeb0c1e3345"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………. no right to use my computer.",
            "description": "Use have with you, we and they.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2b8356e9589405089d6bbe96b5c9a42"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. so much work to do now.",
            "description": "Use have with I.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6b994f3bcee64f47a608ec116a4fc923"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………. a daughter who lives in Canada.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9bbe71cba80948cca46818c9a2502095"
        },
        {
            "question": "What a pleasant surprise! I …………………. no idea you were coming today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ed3332c9dcc64781a0d0027a36c2b5c8"
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………. a wonderful time when we went swimming on the weekend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c9f2999cfab9423b8d60b9c62d2d5820"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………………….. a wonderful time whenever we go swimming.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "21f43a3d1e884ad7a5859c77b6af4bd0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The baby …………………. a slight fever.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7a0f0c0e9f7a4f789ee092769b44e766"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rani …………………. got a fine collection of stamps. She is quite proud of it.",
            "description": "Use has with singular subjects. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6a468c475f5345c4b2eac1913711bf8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………… no excuse for doing this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "50c9e976016a4f2e950bafbe49df2bb9"
        }
    ]
}